Hello, this is Yori Kobayashi. Today, Manatsu-san is, um, about to graduate.
I was invited to the main party.
However, there is only one person here.
Oh, I'm sorry, yes, I'm here, but I'm Manatsu Akimoto.
I'm really sorry.
What happened?
Was today the day you had to get your makeup done? Oh, that's right.
I was shocked to see that Kubo was in perfect condition when I arrived at the site, and I was already in a state of a shaggy mess.
I'm really sorry about that. It gave me time to get ready.
It was such a funny thing. They asked me what I wanted to do at the end of my graduation, and I said I wanted to have a fondue party.
I said I wanted to have a fondue party, but I said I wanted to leave it to others and do my own makeup. It's okay. If you want, one more person isn't coming.
That's right. What's wrong? What happened to that girl?
The other one got to the wrong place. He's on his way.
Well, I'm sorry. I'll be going.
Okay. Have a good day.
I'm going to do my makeup.
See you later.
I'm going to do it.
Then, I'll start cutting the materials.
Let's start right away.
Carrot
I'll just use about 2 carrots.
Potatoes.
I like potatoes.
I'll put a lot of potatoes.
I don't like it when people see me cooking.
I don't like to tell people I'm cooking.
I don't do that much.
It's okay.
It's too heartbreaking.
Thank you for watching.
Oh!
Hey.
I've been waiting for you.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Where's Mr. Maji?
He forgot to put on his makeup and went home.
Just the one?
Yeah.
I see.
I'm glad you're here, and I'm sorry about Shiori.
I just started, you know?
I was so nervous.
I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
Are you sure? We'll do it together.
The snow is here, guys.
I know you've been waiting for me.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I thought it was over.
What are you making?
I was thinking of making a cheese fondue and a chocolate fondue.
I'm working on the ingredients.
Can I have the fondue, then?
Okay, sure.
I have the recipe right here.
Okay.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
You want to take a break?
Not really a break. Stretching.
Stretching? It's an important preparatory exercise.
Here we go.
Are you ready to turn it on?
Is it tiny?
Maybe it's a little tiny.
A clove of garlic.
Yes!
Shall we do garlic?
The more garlic, the better.
Yes, it's good.
Yes, sir.
It's definitely a lot.
Wow!
Too much garlic. Delicious.
Did it say what to do with the garlic?
You cut the garlic in half and rub the cut ends together to release the aroma.
I'll cut it in half.
Okay, please.
Oh, you mean in the pot?
Rub it in, is that what it's supposed to do?
Right here, maybe.
I mean, the garlic cloves cut in half, you mean rubbed right here.
I don't know if that's right.
There we go.
I knew it. Garlic on the nose.
Oh, no! I've been garlic all day!
It's on my nose!
Oh, it smells good.
Oh, it smells good?
That's great.
It's so relaxing.
It's like eating garlic.
I eat so much garlic.
The image of eating garlic is awful.
I mean, it smells like garlic.
I get energy from garlic.
Garlic is delicious.
I love garlic.
If you chop it up, it won't crack.If you chop it up, it won't crack.
If it's chopped.
What's chopped?
You should chop it very fine.
It's next door.
Can I borrow your induction?
Sure.
Oh.
Sorry about that.
I've been waiting.
What's the delay?
You don't say.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, thank God.
I've been waiting for you.
What's the matter?
I told you I'd be late tonight.
I said I'd be late, but he just laughed and sent me on my way.
I said, "Don't laugh at me.
I'm glad you're here.
We're all here.
Thank you, Dr. Kubo.
They're cutting it for me.
All I could do was cut.
That's reassuring.
What should I do?
What did you just do?
I just finished cutting the ingredients.
That's all.
What should I do?
I'm going to boil some carrots.
Start boiling salted water.
I think that's good.
I don't want to boil the asparagus and the carrots together.
Carrots first?
Yes, sir.
Is this okay?
Cheese fondue.
I wanted to have a relaxed party with everyone.
So it turned into a slapstick party.
But I'm glad everyone made it.
I think it's really just a plain party.
It's just too much, isn't it?
Yes, it's too much.
It's so fresh! Yada is holding a knife!
That's right. He only cuts basas.
Are you eating bananas?
Yes, I'm eating them.
You do?
Yes, basas and whales.
Whale?
That's great.
Bananas.
Pumpkins are like this.
It's hard.
The skin.
Soft. Soft.
Wait a minute. I'm scared.
He cut it without holding it.
I'm afraid
The seeds were still there.
What are you eating? What do you eat?
What do you eat?
It's such a mystery.
Rice with egg.
I don't know.
I eat rice with egg every morning, even if I leave at 4:00 a.m.
That's amazing.
Absolutely.
What time do you get up to eat if you leave at 4 a.m.? That's...
Like 3:45.
Oh, my God.
Come here.
You're really good with the last minute.
You get up at that time to eat rice with eggs?
I do.
That's amazing.
What do you eat?
Natto and rice.
Wow, that's great.
It's the best breakfast I've ever had.
Natto is good.
What do you eat? Breakfast.
Miso soup for breakfast.
Good. We all eat Japanese food.
Yes, we do.
I want some miso soup.
You're making it?
I'll make it.
Kubo seems like a decent guy.
Has anyone been to Kubo's house?
No?
But I'm having a pizza party for the graduating seniors.
We're having a pizza party.
What?
Pizza.
Isn't that unusual?
Yes, I like to make pizza.Yes, I like to make pizza.
I can serve pizza.
Uh-huh.
I could help you with the pizza.
What pizza?
Pizza, then.
Anything.
I can make anything.
Any pizza.
Any pizza?
Yes, sir.
That's great.
I can do it.
From the dough?
From the dough.
Oh, my God.
For real?
I'm serious.
Pizza is my specialty.
Oh, my God.
That's cool.
I want you to do it anytime.
I'll do it. I'll do it.
I'll, uh, I'll deliver.
Really?
I'll take you home.
Whatever it takes.
Cuboats.
Uh, microwave.
Oh, no.
Ew.
2 minutes
That's a lot of work.
What, what, what, what?
Are you eating? Are you eating all of a sudden?
No.
It's a bookmark.
I did it.
Kubo gave it to me.
I wanted to see you eat.
Sweet?
You look better when you eat it at night.
It's delicious.
It's like an animal. Are you okay?
An animal. It's really funny.
Where are the strawberries from? This one.
Well, this is a strawberry tom.
Delicious. I haven't eaten any.
Oh, my goodness, he's eating them at random.
Oh, my God, you scared me.
You didn't even eat it.
Can you hold two?
Thank you.
That's it.
All right. It's done.
That's what I'm talking about.
Well, here's to the fondue party.
Shall we eat?
Let's eat!
I wonder if I can dip it.
Oh! It's totally good! Last one!
Looks hot. Careful. Easy to ride.
Looks good! Let's eat.
Yeah! Yum! Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yum! Yum!
That was good!
Yeah! Yum! Yum!
Is it good?
Yeah! - Yeah!
It's good!
Happy! Happy!
Yum!
Gorgeous!
Delicious!
There are so many ingredients!
As many as you want!
Yes!
It's true!
Such a gorgeous dish!
I want to invite everyone!
Right!
Yes, indeed!
If you really want to come, please come.
Come on, come on.
I'm so glad.
Yeah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
How can you do that?
How can you look so innocent?
Are you a genius?
What was that look?
What did you look like?
Hmm?
Oh, okay, okay.
I'm trying, I'm fectured.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Boo-boo is cute. He's so cute.Boo-boo is cute. He's so cute.
Mushroom turn then!
I waited so long. I told him I'd eat shrooms and he said I was cute.
I'm sure it's a woman's lie but it's terrible I thought she'd never pick up on it
I don't know anything about it.
Is it hot? Cute.
I don't know. She called me cute at the exact right moment.
Mmm. Cute.
I like it. Happy.
Peace.
I wish it could go on forever.
I really do.
It's fun.
Miyan, what do you do on your days off?
I seriously sleep.
I'm the type of person who lets the day go by without doing anything.
I see.
The other day, I finished work early.
I was at the same site as Yuki, and we had to do some rehearsal stuff today.
We were talking about how we had to go home and do things individually.
So we went home and sat on the futon for 6 hours, saying, "Go, go, go," and the day was over.
Six hours. Six hours, really.
Six hours?
I kept telling myself to work hard for six hours, and the day was over.
You didn't sleep?
No, I didn't. I was really saying that. I kept telling myself to work hard, work hard.
What, six hours?
I'm scared, scared, scared.
Are you okay? Of course I'm worried.
I'm scared.
It's going to be over before we can do anything.
It'll be over.
It really is.
What are you doing?
I don't know what I'm doing.
I haven't lived until now, so I went out to dinner and karaoke with my juniors.
I went out to dinner and karaoke with my junior.
Who's that?
Don't tell anyone.
You're not telling?
Wait, there's only so many juniors I can go with.
Ask him about his juniors.
Can I guess?
If I guess, will you tell me?
It's a secret.
What's that?
What's up with you all of a sudden?
I'm the type of person who likes to hide things.
The type that wants to hide?
The type that wants to hide it.
Do you make reservations at the restaurant?
Yes, I do.
That's great.
He's my senior.
You're a senior.
No, I'm not. No, you're not.
Farewell, Farewell.
I'm relieved. I don't need to worry about that.
Have fun.
That's great.
You don't seem like much of a senior, do you?
That's why I can have fun.
I feel like I'm like Minomi.
I don't know.
The way you keep your distance from your juniors.
Aren't we a bit alike?
Yes, we are.
You talk to them in a flat way.
Don't act like you're the senior.
No, I don't feel like a senior even if I try my best.
No, I don't.
It's like we're on the same level.
When you had a potluck at the restaurant, did you talk a lot?
Did you talk a lot?
Yes, we did.
The whole time.
We talked a lot.
About trivial things.
Really.
I want to mix.
I want to mix with you.
But I'm afraid of being exposed.
You know, that's something you've been saying a lot lately, in front of me.
If I see your true nature, I'll hate you.
What kind of real person are you?
I think you're a really beautiful person.
I don't even know what he looks like?
Maybe not.
Really?
Do I know him? I've been trying to show her a lot.
But I feel like Manachi-san is about to cross that line. In my mind.
What do you mean? What do you mean?
It's a very good thing, and as a result of thinking that we've become very close on our own, I've been thinking that we've become too friendly.
As a result of thinking that we have become very good friends, we have become too close, and I feel like I'm going to cross this line of not wanting to be disliked. I'm afraid of that.
That's what I'm afraid of.
You mean you are afraid of showing too much?
Yes, that's right. Yes, that's right.
That's good.
It's good?Oh, you don't mind?
I thought I didn't want to graduate with you hating me.
I really, I'm not lying, I really, really dislike people. I'm absolutely fine.
I'm not afraid. I'm absolutely fine.
Really?
I'm sure.
Then let's get out of here.
You don't want me to?
Now, now, let it out now.
Not just me, the whole world.
I'm really not a smart person, really.
I don't feel like partying.
What's that? You mean like a Parisian?
No, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's just that the tension is a little weird.
I know.
Yeah, I know.
Really?
If I knew, I would have left.
Everyone knows, I guess.
Hey, you know, there are times when you say to yourself, "I'm in a douchey mood"?
Yes, that's it. That's it.
Is it showing?
Oh, it's coming out.
I'm self-reporting.
I say, "I'm sorry, I'm feeling a little annoyed today.
That's good.
I think it's good.
If you only look at my solid side, you'll think I'm really a terrible person.
That's not true.
Kabo is around here and I feel like I'm already around here.
I'll be around here.
You see, gradually, there is a difference.
If the kabosu comes down, we'll be there, too.
I'm not just above you, but...
I really can't believe you're younger than me.
I see.
When we have this conversation, I'm sure everyone hears about it.
Like this.
I can say it to myself, but everyone around me says, "Oh, really?
I've done this about 100 times in 6 years.
I'm getting used to it.
I am 22.
I'm 21.
I've done one.
You're from a rural area, so you always stayed in an I-room when you lived in a hotel.
Oh, really?
I see.
Not you?
You didn't? You always woke me up.
I did?
You're the one who does big things like that.
Momoko and Den are in the same room, and usually Yuda and I are in the same room.
I'm really shocked.
I took so many pictures.
I don't know.
No, I don't remember this.
I'll send you a picture.
Send it.
Send it, send it.
Do you want to try the food book?
Shall we?
Let's do this one.
Looks delicious.
It's cute.
Is it hot? It looks hot.
Mmm! Mmm! Yummy! Mmm!
I'm sorry, I said the guy in the back first.
He took my comment.
Please eat.
How about you, Yuki? It's delicious.
Oh, it's good.
It's good.
I think marshmallows and chips would be delicious together.
Sweet and salty. It's absolutely delicious.
Delicious!
Let's give it a try!
Oh, my gosh!
Wow, this is great.
Oh, I see.
I've never seen that before.
Looks good.
It's a little unappealing, though.
I thought so.
Are you sure you don't want to?
Wait, wait, wait.
You breathe too much before you eat.
You eat like a bitch.
I remembered the vacuum cleaner.
I regret it so much.
Yum! It's absolutely delicious!
It's so good!
Bon appétit!
Yes!
I'll go wipe my mouth.
Mmm! Yum!
Tasty?Delicious?
I love mayonnaise so much!
Chocolate banana.
Yeah, it's good.
Absolutely delicious.
Yeah, it'll last.
What? What's that?
Oh, it'll hold.
Oh.
Okay, bye.
Okay.
Ah!
I got it.
Mmm!
Mmm~!
I wish this could go on forever.
Hey, are you going to read it later?
Oh, no.
I want to stop.
Hey, stop.
Sure, sure. I'm not going to stop. I'm never going home.
Oh, no, no, no.
I thought you had another job.
Nice balance. Third year.
This is how it is in the third trimester. Always.
It's funny.
But I remember something really well.
I remember Manatsu-san saying...
I don't know...
Every time a member of the senior class graduates
Manatsu-san's motivation
gradually decreases, right?
And at that time, Manatsu-san's loneliness
I guess your loneliness must have reached a certain point.
I think she was already
I think she was crying at the school.
She said, "I'm going to lose my neighbor at the school.
I'm going to lose my neighbor at the school, so please come and live next to me.
Did he say that?
I was sobbing my eyes out to the third-term students.
I'm going to have no one to talk to at school.
I'm going to have no one to talk to.
I remember it so well.
I'm sorry.
I was so happy.
And I was really happy.
It really became true.
I saw the third term students in the dressing room with Manatsu-san.
I saw the third-term students in the dressing room with Ms. Manatsu.
I felt that what I said at that time had become true.
I was so happy.
It was amazing.
I'm so grateful.
Hey.
Thank you. You took a lot of pictures.
You took a lot of pictures?
Don't you call them "high quality"?
If you take a lot of pictures...
You're so cute.
Nice shots.
It's only for the game, so it's all we have.
Yeah, I know, right?
Let's do it in private.
See you later.
I'll buy a bunch of games.
Really?
I have a lot of games too.
What?
I'll go get them.
What? I really want to play.
I really want to.
Sooner or later.
But you know what?
This guy...
He won't invite me.
Me, too. I don't talk about other people.
He doesn't ask me out.
Yeah, at a time like this.
I don't show it much.
I don't let my mean-spiritedness come out.
I'm a real pain in the ass.
I'm a pain in the ass.
Are you drunk?
Is this okay?
I'm on the upper level of the path.
Is everything okay?
I'm a pain in the ass.
Very.
You know that, don't you?
I know that.
Well, you know.
I'm a pain in the ass, really.
I don't know.
I want to ask you out, but...
But if I ask you out...
I don't know why you're spending so much time with me.I'm sorry you have to spend so much time with me.
I'm sorry I'm looking for something.
And I talk too much.
Why are you making me cry?
Why? Why?
What? Why?
I'm just so surprised.
I knew I'd come this far without asking you out.
Why not?
Well, it's a pain in the ass.
I feel like I have to change.
But I can't change.
When did you start?
It's never too late to start.
You're right.
I really can't ask people out.
You're really crying.
Yeah, I'm kind of...
You know...
I'm full of regrets.
Hey, hey...
Hey, hey, hey.
Okay, I'll ask you out.
Look, it doesn't matter if you can't ask me out.
There are people who will ask you out.
But I want to invite them.
That's why some things are so annoying.
Huh?
There are things that are a pain in the ass.
I know it's a pain in the ass.
This is not the point.
It's this aspect of it.
It's great.
Oh, no.
I cried at the part where I didn't know what it meant.
It's not like that.
It's just...
I'm sorry.
I feel so lame.
You're so lame as a human being.
No, I'm not.
There's no such thing as a lame person.
I don't know what to do.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Wait, I don't understand.
Oh, my God!
This is too much fun.
You're cute.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I can't go back.
It's okay.
I'll eat.
I don't know how to feel about this.
Don't eat all of a sudden.
On the contrary, don't eat.
You're eating while crying.
Finish this first, then eat.
You're right.
Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
It's okay.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I'm starting to feel human.
It's better that way.
It's a good thing.
So, Manatsu, after you graduate...
She won't be a member of Nogizaka anymore.
So if you want to talk to a member about it...
I'm not sure if it's too difficult for you right now or not.
Manatsu-senpai will be just an older sister.
Well...
I'll miss her, but...
It's better to be just an older sister.
I don't have to worry about it
My sensibilities are fine.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
If I say something here...
I'll tell you everything.
Today's the day of secrecy.
I'll tell you in secret.
Sneak.
Okay. - Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
It's nothing... if you don't talk too much.
You know what?
What were you going to say?
I'm going to say I love you.
I'll tell you what I was going to say.
I'm over milk.
Surprise!
But it's really true.
It's true.
You're all too good to me?
Please make sure you receive them properly before you graduate.
This girl's.This child's
It's nothing, I don't cry.
You're kidding?
Why not?
I know.
Yes, I do.
It's not so bad.
I can't do it anymore.
I might not make it anymore.
You said blue.
It's not there if you talk too much.
I know, I know.
I thought everyone would cry.
Yuki, I know.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean for you to cry.
I know. I understand.
I hate it.
I'm going to say it. I'm going to tell you.
Are you okay, Acchan?
Just in case.
Just in case. For the camera. It's on the TV.
I know, I know.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing.
If you miss me like that, I'll be tempted to extend it by six months or something.
Extend it.
I really don't mind if you extend it.
I mean, if you guys miss me, you know.
I usually like you guys.
If I'm having a hard time.
If you have a hard time, you might think about telling them until everything is resolved.
But I like you so much that I do.
I'm glad.
I really like you, don't I?
I really like you, Manatsu-san.
Me too.
No good.
We're alone now.
Did you find tissues over there?
Wait a minute.
You've had them all along. From before.
I told you that hurts.
Here, I'll blow my nose with a soft tissue.
My nose.
I know. I really understand.
It's you, Yuki-san.
Not at all.
Guri.
I'm glad.
I'll miss you. I'm a samurai, so I'll put my goo at your feet and clench my fists.
I'm whitening my head. Let's make it white.
I've never heard of whitening anything. Go for it.
Yuki, I'll whiten it.
Come on, come on. It's okay. It's okay.
Hey, wait a minute. Don't cheer me up.
I didn't mean it like this. We should have fun.
I came with that intention, too. I regretted not asking you out.
I felt like I'm human. I thought I loved you.
I totally understand, don't worry, there's always more to come
You're still 29, so there's a lot more to come
You're right, I can't go into that
I can't go into that. Right now, I felt a momentary hesitation in my eyes.
If you've been together for seven years, you'll be able to see the hesitation in their eyes
You caught on.
You're going to eat that? Strawberries with gusto! You're an otter!
That's funny. Thank you.
I'm glad you're here today.
I'll love you for the rest of my life.
Thank you.
I'm glad you're smiling.
And now... please don't slap me in the face when I'm about to close.
Well... the two of them came to the Pondu party, and it was a bit of a slapstick show at first, but it ended like this.
But it ended like this... we talked a lot and had a nice dinner... it was really fun.
I was really happy, and when I'm with the 3rd term students, I'm just my true self, so...
I really hope we can continue to be friends in the future.
Please subscribe to our channel and like us!
Please subscribe to our channel, like us, and click the "Good" button.